<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Egg on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/recipebook/tags/egg/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Egg on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/recipebook/tags/egg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tomato Egg Prawn Stirfry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipebook/posts/tomato_egg_prawn_stirfry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipebook/posts/tomato_egg_prawn_stirfry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;3 very large tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;500g prawns&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;6 eggs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;5 cloves of garlic, minced or chopped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;4 spring onions, sliced and separated in two, half ingredient half garnish&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp oyster sauce&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 tsp sesame oil&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 tsp sugar&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 tsp chicken stock&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1/2 tsp chicken salt&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1/2 tsp pepper&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp corn starch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;4 tbsp water&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Put the rice cooker on in advance&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mix together the sauce by combining oyster sauce, sesame oil, sugar, chicken stock, salt and pepper.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Scramble the eggs, season lightly with salt and pepper&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In a pan with some oil, cook the eggs until just done, fluffy, moist. Take them off and put aside.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Clean out the pan, then again with some oil, cook the garlic and half the spring onion for a minute.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add the prawns.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;When the prawns are almost done, add the sauce we made earlier and the tomatos. Cook until they have broken down and a release the juice.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Make a slurry by combining the corn starch and water, and add it. Stir until thickened&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add in the scrambled eggs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Plate ontop of rice, garnish with the remaining spring onion.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oyakodon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipebook/posts/oyakodon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipebook/posts/oyakodon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 cups (500ml) dashi stock&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;60ml sake&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;30ml soy sauce, plus more to taste&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;30g sugar, plus more to taste&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 large onions (~300g), thinly sliced&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;600g boneless, skinless chicken thighs, chopped to bitesize pieces&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;4 green onions, sliced, divided in 2 (optional; see note)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;~6 large eggs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;togarashi (japanese chilli powder) (optional; garnish/seasoning)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;rice&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Combine dashi, sake, soy sauce, and sugar in a 10-inch skillet and bring to a simmer over high heat. Adjust heat to maintain a strong simmer. Stir in onion and cook, stirring occasionally, until onion is half tender, about 5 minutes. Add chicken pieces and cook, stirring and turning chicken occasionally, until chicken is cooked through and broth has reduced by about half, 5 to 7 minutes for chicken thighs or 3 to 4 minutes for chicken breast. Stir in half of scallions and all of mitsuba (if using), then season broth to taste with more soy sauce or sugar as desired. The sauce should have a balanced sweet-and-salty flavor.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reduce heat to a bare simmer. Pour beaten eggs into skillet in a thin, steady stream, holding chopsticks over edge of bowl to help distribute eggs evenly (see video above). Cover and cook until eggs are cooked to desired doneness, about 1 minute for runny eggs or 3 minutes for medium-firm.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To Serve - transfer hot rice to a single large bowl or 2 individual serving bowls. Top with egg and chicken mixture, pouring out any excess broth from saucepan over rice. Add an extra egg yolk to center of each bowl, if desired (see note). Garnish with remaining sliced scallions and togarashi. Serve immediately.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
