<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chicken on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/recipebook/tags/chicken/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chicken on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/recipebook/tags/chicken/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Oyakodon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipebook/posts/oyakodon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipebook/posts/oyakodon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 cups (500ml) dashi stock&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;60ml sake&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;30ml soy sauce, plus more to taste&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;30g sugar, plus more to taste&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 large onions (~300g), thinly sliced&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;600g boneless, skinless chicken thighs, chopped to bitesize pieces&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;4 green onions, sliced, divided in 2 (optional; see note)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;~6 large eggs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;togarashi (japanese chilli powder) (optional; garnish/seasoning)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;rice&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Combine dashi, sake, soy sauce, and sugar in a 10-inch skillet and bring to a simmer over high heat. Adjust heat to maintain a strong simmer. Stir in onion and cook, stirring occasionally, until onion is half tender, about 5 minutes. Add chicken pieces and cook, stirring and turning chicken occasionally, until chicken is cooked through and broth has reduced by about half, 5 to 7 minutes for chicken thighs or 3 to 4 minutes for chicken breast. Stir in half of scallions and all of mitsuba (if using), then season broth to taste with more soy sauce or sugar as desired. The sauce should have a balanced sweet-and-salty flavor.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reduce heat to a bare simmer. Pour beaten eggs into skillet in a thin, steady stream, holding chopsticks over edge of bowl to help distribute eggs evenly (see video above). Cover and cook until eggs are cooked to desired doneness, about 1 minute for runny eggs or 3 minutes for medium-firm.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To Serve - transfer hot rice to a single large bowl or 2 individual serving bowls. Top with egg and chicken mixture, pouring out any excess broth from saucepan over rice. Add an extra egg yolk to center of each bowl, if desired (see note). Garnish with remaining sliced scallions and togarashi. Serve immediately.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easy Chicken Curry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipebook/posts/easy_chicken_curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipebook/posts/easy_chicken_curry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1kg chicken breast/thighs, cut into cubes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 onions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;3 garlic cloves, grated&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1 knob ginger, grated&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;3 tablespoons vegetable oil&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 tablespoon curry powder&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1.5 teaspoons salt&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1/2 teaspoon black pepper&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;4 large tomatoes, chopped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1 can (400g) coconut cream/milk&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;180ml water&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;½ teaspoon garam masala&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Coriander (chopped for garnish)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In a large pan heat oil. Add chopped onions and sauté until golden, over medium-low heat. stir occasionally.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;When onions are golden add garlic and ginger. Stir and cook for 2 minutes. Add chopped tomatoes and cook, stirring occasionally, until soft. Add curry powder and cook, stirring, for 2 minutes. Add chicken breast, season with salt and pepper, cook for 5 minutes, until golden. Cover the pan and cook for 2-3 minutes more. Add water, cover and cook 10 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add coconut milk/cream, season with garam masala and salt, stir, and cook until lightly thickens.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Serve with naan bread or rice.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
