<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prawn on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/recipebook/tags/prawn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prawn on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/recipebook/tags/prawn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chilli Wine Garlic Prawn Pasta</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipebook/recipes/chilli_wine_garlic_prawn_pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipebook/recipes/chilli_wine_garlic_prawn_pasta/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1kg prawns&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;360g linguine or similar&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;3 shallot, diced or half a white onion&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 red chilli, deseeded and diced&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;400 grams cherry tomatoes, halved&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;5 cloves garlic, finely sliced&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1 cup white wine,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp unsalted butter&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;zest of 2 lemon&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp fresh chopped parsley&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;40 grams grated parmesan cheese plus extra for serving if desired&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bring a large pot of salted water to boil for cooking the pasta.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add the butter to a frying pan over medium heat and, if using raw prawns, add them to the pan and cook until they just turn pink. Remove the prawns and set aside, leaving the butter in the pan.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add the shallot and chilli to the pan with the butter and saute. Meanwhile, put the pasta on to cook.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;When the shallot begins to soften (2-3 minutes) add the garlic and tomatoes to the pan with a pinch of salt and pepper. Stir together then pour over the wine.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Allow the sauce to simmer for about 5 minutes until the pasta is cooked. It should be slightly al dente (use the lower cooking time recommended on the packet).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add the prawns into the pan with the chilli and tomato, give everything a stir and add the pasta. (I prefer to use tongs to transfer the pasta directly into the sauce. This also adds some of the pasta water which will emulsify the sauce and help it stick to the pasta. If you prefer to drain the pasta first in a colander, make sure to keep a tablespoon of the cooking water and add it to the sauce with the pasta.)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sprinkle over the parsley, parmesan and lemon zest and toss everything together with tongs before serving.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Serve with an extra sprinkle of parmesan and a side of salad.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomato Egg Prawn Stirfry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipebook/recipes/tomato_egg_prawn_stirfry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipebook/recipes/tomato_egg_prawn_stirfry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;3 very large tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;500g prawns&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;6 eggs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;5 cloves of garlic, minced or chopped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;4 spring onions, sliced and separated in two, half ingredient half garnish&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp oyster sauce&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 tsp sesame oil&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 tsp sugar&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 tsp chicken stock&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1/2 tsp chicken salt&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1/2 tsp pepper&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp corn starch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;4 tbsp water&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Put the rice cooker on in advance&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mix together the sauce by combining oyster sauce, sesame oil, sugar, chicken stock, salt and pepper.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Scramble the eggs, season lightly with salt and pepper&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In a pan with some oil, cook the eggs until just done, fluffy, moist. Take them off and put aside.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Clean out the pan, then again with some oil, cook the garlic and half the spring onion for a minute.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add the prawns.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;When the prawns are almost done, add the sauce we made earlier and the tomatos. Cook until they have broken down and a release the juice.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Make a slurry by combining the corn starch and water, and add it. Stir until thickened&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add in the scrambled eggs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Plate ontop of rice, garnish with the remaining spring onion.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Serve with rice&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
